takoomi.com 2016-04-10

# Privacy Policy | Takoomi.com - Daring Technology. Mobile Superiority

**Global Privacy Policy**

Takoomi (the “Company” or “We”) is committed to protect the privacy of users who access its Website (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy Statement (the “Privacy Policy”) explains the types of information We gather and what We do with it. By using the Site and through our Takoomi platform. 

The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Takoomi. You must agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, including our use of cookies in order to: a) access or use our Site; and/or (b) subscribe to any of the Takoomi platform, products and/or services (the “Services”) offered on the Site (each, a “Subscription”). Your acceptance of both this Privacy Policy and our use of cookies on the Site shall be deemed a blanket acceptance of such Privacy Policy and cookie usage for all future attempts to access the Site and/or any Subscription of the Services. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to become a subscriber (“Subscriber”) to the Services and/or use the Site in any manner or form whatsoever. 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@takoomi.com](mailto:support@takoomi.com). 

COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

We collect the following personal information from you when you sign up for our service: Name, Company Name, Website, address, email address, phone number and mobile number.

We may also collect information about other users you wish to add to your account, such information includes: Name, title, office number and email address.

We may also collect certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, your Internet Service Provider, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring Website addresses, your email address, and your passwords.

We may also collect information about your mobile devices, including your cell phone or other mobile device number and model, and your cellular carrier.

We may also collect information about which pages you visit on our Website.

If you apply for a job on our site we will collect your name, email address, phone number and resume. We use this information to contact you regarding the position in which you had applied and to determine if you are a good candidate for the position.

If you wish to share a job post with your friend, we will collect their name and email address. We use this information to send them a one-time email inviting them to view the invite. We do not store this information for any reason.

USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. 

We may use your personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To ensure our Website is relevant to your needs and to make the Website easier for you to use. 

  * To operate the Platform, maintain quality of the service, improve our Website and Services, and provide general statistics regarding use of our Website. 

  * To deliver products and services, including newsletters and email notifications, confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages that you request or purchase, and to process payments that you have agreed to make for those products and services. 

  * To help us create and publish content and offer products most relevant to you. 

  * To alert you to our products and services, new products, special offers and promotions, updated information and other new or updated services that may be offered by Takoomi and our selected partners. 

  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our Website as appropriate. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt-out by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing is at [support@takoomi.com](mailto:support@takoomi.com)

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. 

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, and in the Agreement, Takoomi will not rent, sell, or share personally identifiable information collected on the Website or through the Platform with other people or nonaffiliated companies unless we have your consent, or under the following circumstances:  

  * to protect the rights and property of Takoomi, our agents, customers, users, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use; 

  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work for us and need access to your information to do their work such as providing customer support, processing payments, and storing data (e.g. AWS). Any third-party vendor so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by Takoomi; 

  * in an emergency to protect the personal safety of Takoomi, its customers, or any person; 

  * We may occasionally allow other companies to offer our customers information about their products and services, but only when we believe that a significant number of our customers would be interested in receiving the information. If you do not want to receive email offers from us or from third parties, follow the procedure described in the emails or contact us at [support@takoomi.com](mailto:support@takoomi.com)

We may also share aggregated or anonymized information in a form that does not directly identify you or your End Users with any third parties. 

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or court order or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. In addition, information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets of the company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information 

Parents are able to consent to our use of their child’s Personal Information without having also to consent to our disclosure of their child’s Personal Information to third parties as we will not share any information collected about a child through our client’s services with third parties. 

ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

If you wish to correct or delete any personal information we have collected, please log into your account and change the information. You may also remove your information from the viewable web pages by closing your account, or you may make a request to us by email at [support@takoomi.com](mailto:support@takoomi.com) . We will process your requested changes, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable time after receipt of the request, normally not to exceed three business days. We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

If you would like access, update or request deletion of your child’s personal information, please contact our Client that you or your child have been interacting with to do so. Parent’s may refuse further contact with their child by contacting our Client directly.

SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use reasonable efforts including a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number or bank account information) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. However, we cannot guarantee that your personal information will be absolutely protected. For example, your personal information may be affected by actions outside of our control, such as computer "hacking" and physical theft. In these anomalous situations, we will try to rectify the anomaly as soon as we can.

You acknowledge that you provide your personal information to Takoomi with knowledgeable consent and at your own risk.

COLLECTION AND USE OF END USER ANALYTICS INFORMATION.

The Platform provides information to you about how your End Users use online browsing and their mobile applications as well as how applications are performing across different mobile devices (but the Platform does not collect personally identifiable information about your End Users). Takoomi obtains this information either directly from our Customers (typically with the use of advertising links) or from our Software Development Kit (“SDK”) if embedded by you in an End User's mobile application.

The data collected may include: agent version, platform, SDK version, timestamp, API key (identifier for application), application version, device identifier—e.g., MAC address, Android ID, and IFA—Model, manufacture and OS version of device, session start/stop time, locale (specific location where a given language is spoken), time zone, and network status (WiFi, etc.). The device identifiers may be hashed. In addition, Takoomi may collect the following data if you select the option for Takoomi to collect and provide such data to Takoomi: anonymous User ID, latitude and longitude, events, errors, and page views. Finally, we see the IP address of the user through the HTTP request. Takoomi uses this data to create reports for you to analyze your End Users and to create reports and/or metrics against which you can compare your user base. We may provide you with the option of exporting raw Takoomi data to your servers such as timestamp, platform, event, and user ID. You can also record errors that occur in your applications and receive an export of data containing the error information.

Your End User data is presented to you to analyze your applications. In addition, Takoomi may provide you with aggregated and anonymous benchmark data that includes your End User data and all other Customers' End User data.  **But while Takoomi assists you with the organization and collection of End User data, Takoomi specifically disclaims ownership of this data. The End User data stored by our servers belongs exclusively to our Customers and may be deleted any time at their request.**

CUSTOMER USE OF END USER DATA.

takoomi is not responsible for any use by you of any data about your End Users, even if Takoomi helped you collect the data. You should allow End Users to review your policies to understand your use of End User data. You are prohibited from using the Platform, Services, or Website to independently collect any personally identifiable information about any End User. Further, you must provide a privacy agreement to your End Users in which written notice is given to the End Users that they may opt out of Takoomi Analytics tracking by sending an email to [support@takoomi.com](mailto:support@takoomi.com)

In the event that you are aware, or should be aware of, the potential for users of your Subscription website to access such from any European Union state, you agree to comply with the 2009/136/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council Directive, commonly known as the “EU Cookie Directive”, that requires websites to obtain informed consent from internet users before storing information on such internet users’ computers or any web-connected devices. Further, you agree to amend your privacy policy as necessary to maintain compliance with any supplemental laws, regulations or directives that may be enacted from time to time by legislative bodies and that may pertain to your use of the Services and your Subscription website.

END USER OPT-OUT PROVISION.

Your End Users can opt-out of Takoomi Analytics tracking and personalized ads/recommendations from Takoomi by sending an email to [support@takoomi.com](mailto:support@takoomi.com).

The opt-out is specific to Takoomi’s activities and does not affect the activities of other ad networks or analytics providers that you use. If an End User opts-out, Takoomi will stop tracking data for that device identifier going forward. The Takoomi Analytics tracking will stop across all applications. Takoomi will stop providing recommendations to the device identifier across all publishers.

There may be a short delay of up to several business days while the request is being verified, processed, and deployed across our system.

USE OF COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS.

**Cookies: To enhance your experience with the Website, we use “cookies.” You cannot use this Website or the Services without agreeing to accept the cookies that we use with the Site.**

Cookies are small packets of data stored on your computer. Cookies are used by your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. We use cookies to understand Website usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Website. When someone visits our Website, we may place a cookie on the user's device (if the user accepts cookies) or may read a cookie already in place if the user has visited the Website previously. You may set your browser to warn you that cookies are in use, or to block the use of cookies. Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If your browser is not set to accept cookies, certain uses of the Website may require you to go to your browser user preferences to enable cookies. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from this Website, you will be able to view the text on the screens. However you may not be able to experience a personalized visit. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you change computers, operating systems or browsers, or use multiple computers or browsers, you will need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser. To find out more about cookies, please visit the links at the end of this privacy policy.

The use of third party cookies is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

Web beacons: We may or our third party tracking utility partner may collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Website, in our Services, or in our emails. Our use of Web beacons includes to deliver cookies, to count visits and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon. (A Web beacon is also sometimes called a Web bug or a pixel tag or a clear GIF.) We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

USE OF THIRD PARTY LINKS. 

The Website may contain links to third-party websites (“Third Party Websites”). Please be aware that Takoomi is not responsible for the privacy practices of Third Party Websites. We encourage you, when you leave our Website, to read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Takoomi. 

Social Media (Features) and Widgets 

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider 

You can log in to our support section of the site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.  Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.   

DATA RETENTION. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support@takoomi.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF DATA. 

In the process of providing services to you, we may transfer information that we collect about you or your End Users, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you or your End Users are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring information and permitting the transfer of information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction. You consent to the transfer of your information to the United States and the use and disclosure of information about you and your End Users, including personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

CONTACT INFORMATION. 

If you have any questions, comments or suggestions about this Privacy Policy or the practices relating to this Website, or other questions about privacy, please contact us at support@takoomi.com or by mail to Takoomi Ltd, 5 Ha’arad St, RDT Building, Tel Aviv. 62667, ISRAEL. or by telephone at 972-527024132. 

INFORMATION RELATED TO DATA COLLECTED THROUGH THE Takoomi PLATFORM 

Takoomi collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. 

Choice 

We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly. 

Service Provider, Sub-Processors/Onward Transfer 

Takoomi may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients. 

Access to Data Controlled by our Clients 

Takoomi has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his or her query to Takoomi Client (the data controller). If the Client requests Takoomi to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days. 

Data Retention 

Takoomi will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Takoomi will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
